本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：装汁的容器    Soomii    红豆包    Iz
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第八集
■
画展
我记得去年的画展老悲催了
Wow, I thought last year's art crawl was terrible,
-今年的要好很多  是吧  -是啊
- but they really outdid themselves this year, huh? -Yeah.
悲壳  骇马
在海边  别疯癫
-真恶心  -恶心死了
- Ugh, bad. -Very bad.
咱们走  海鸥鸥
瞅那个  简直没法看
Oh, look at that. Really bad.
我要被刺瞎了
Really, really bad.
我觉得  还不错啊
I think they're... good.
老爸  为什么街区画展办得这么操蛋
Dad, why does art crawl suck so much?
这种画展对作品的质量要求不高  露易丝
Well, it's just a very loose definition of art, Louise.
还有  不许你说"操蛋"
And don't say "suck".
请您别用  "操蛋"
Don't say "suck", please.
不过你说得对  的确很操蛋
You're right, though. It does suck.
我可不想让你们认为这就是所谓的"艺术"
I don't want you kids to think this is what art is.
咱们应该去美术馆看看
We should go to a museum.
-应该去你个头  -别闹了
- We should not go to a museum. - Let's not overdo it.
-咱还是逛逛画展吐吐槽吧  -同意
- Let's just walk around and make fun of this stuff. - Yeah.
我们为什么不回餐馆
Why don't we just go back to the restaurant?
因为你小姨盖尔正往墙上钉画呢
Because your Aunt Gayle is there hanging up her art,
她的神作可不允许被亵渎
which we're not allowed to make fun of at all.
为啥不能拿盖尔姨妈的画逗逗乐
Well, why can't we make fun of Aunt Gayle's paintings?
-她又不是外人  -是啊
- She's family. - Yeah.
家人就是要坦诚相对嘛  你腋下湿了
That means never holding back anything, right, pit stains?
能看着吗
Am I showing?
你的衬衫跟我身上的内裤一样  全是汗渍
Let's just say your shirt looks like my underwear right now.
听好了  谁也不许对盖尔说打击人的话
Yeah. Well, look, no one tells Gayle anything she can't handle.
这是你们老妈的规定  知道了吗
That's your mom's rule, all right?
你们要像对待精神病一样对待她
You treat her like a mental patient.
她本来就是精神病  是吧
Well, I mean, she probably should be one, right?
是啊  我听说有一次她把自己的口红吃了
Yeah, I heard she ate her lipstick once
因为她想感受一下内在的"激情"
because she wanted to feel "red" inside.
她还用活虾做了件连衣裙穿到外面去秀
And she made a dress out of live shrimp and wore it to mass.
她还给猫剃胡子呢
Oh, and she shaved her cat.
行了  露易丝  你知道这些都不是真的
Come on, Louise. You know none of that is true.
除了给猫剃胡子
Except for the cat shaving.
还有活虾连衣裙  还有吃口红
And maybe the shrimp. And the lipstick.
坑爹呢么  我孩子都能画出来这种画
Are you kidding me? My kid could paint that.
出售
这幅画卖200块钱
Wow. It costs $200.
怎么会有人买这货
Someone bought that mess?!
太没礼貌了
How rude!
哈罗德
Harold!
-哈罗德  -干嘛
- Harold?!  - What?
有几个没教养的死小孩对着我们的画指手画脚
There are some poorly supervised children amongst the art.
-把他们都轰走  -没问题
- Get rid of them! - All right.
走  赶紧走
Let's go. Keep moving.
请问  你是门卫吗
Excuse me. Are you a-- are you a bouncer?
你会让我的孩子骑你大腿吗
Are you gonna bounce my kids?
不  不  快点离开  胖坨
No, no. Just keep it moving, chubs.
-胖坨  -你们可以不回家
- Chubs? - You don't have to go home,
但是不能待在这儿
but you can't stay here.
别激动  老家伙  少碰我
Hey, easy, pal, all right? Don't touch.
算了  老爸  跟这种人犯不上
Come on, dad. This guy's not worth it.
-乖乖听你孩子的  肥仔  -肥仔
- Ah, listen to your kids, fatsy. - Fatsy?
-算了  算了  老爸  -露易丝
-Come on. Come on, dad. -Louise...
爸  看我  眼睛看着我
Dad, look at me. Give me your eyes, dad.
爸  看着我
Give me your eyes.
深呼吸  算你走运  老家伙
Take a deep breath. You are lucky, pal.
跟他犯不上  爸
It's not worth it, dad.
你要是打他  会惹一手药膏和尿骚味
If you hit him, your hand would smell like ointment and pee.
你才有药膏和尿骚味呢
You smell like ointment and pee.
你有药膏和尿骚味
-你有药膏和尿骚味  -你...
- You smell like ointment and pee. - You...
刚才可真尴尬
Well, that was awkward.
那是家什么店啊
What is that place?
你没听说过"激情四射"吗
You don't know "Reflections"?
他们家卖画
They sell art,
不只在画展期间  全年都卖
not just during art crawl, but year-round.
激情四射
Reflections.
瞅你给人家说得  都说成脱衣舞会了
It sounds like a strip club, the way you say it.
激情四射
Reflections.
好了  准备好迎接盖尔姨妈的画展吧
So, brace yourselves for Aunt Gayle's art show.
老妈说  盖尔姨妈告诉她
Mom said Aunt Gayle told her
她画的只是一些可爱的小动物
they're just adorable animals.
是吗  听起来还不至于那么糟糕
Oh, yeah? Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
亲爱的  画展怎么样
Hi, hon! How was art crawl?
这里一切都很好  我们玩得很开心
Huh? Everything's going great here. We're having fun.
-琳  -盖尔在这儿呢
-Lin... -Gayle's here!
我们在墙上挂满了她的画
We hung-hung her paintings!
看这个  看那个
Look at this one! Look at that one!
琳达  你就让我瞅...  苍天啊
Linda, can you just let me see... Oh, my God!
好耶  屁眼屁眼
Yeah! Anuses!
苍天啊  大地啊  琳
Oh, God. Oh, my God, Lin.
就展示几天  鲍鲍
It's a few days, Bobby.
琳达  咱这墙上全都是动物的屁眼
Linda, there are animal anuses all over our walls.
忽略屁眼  光看小翘臀就行了
Just think of 'em as cute little rumps.
琳  你叫我怎么忽略
Lin, they're anuses.
让我来想想有没有更恶心的餐厅装饰画
I'm trying to think of worse paintings to hang in a restaurant.
不  我想不出更恶心的
Um... nope, I can't think of any.
-你个臭猴子  -孩子们  快停下
- Bad monkey! - Kids, stop that.
不要  我在打它的屁股
No. I'm spanking the monkey!
歇菜吧  老爸
No way, dad.
这是我们经历过的最美妙的事
This is the best thing that has ever happened to us.
马屁股
Horse butt.
你好  先生
Oh, hello, sir.
请别看墙上那些屁眼画
Don't look at the pictures of the anus...
他已经看到了  好吧
Yup, he already did. Okay.
看见没  琳
You see that, Lin?
谁被屁眼盯着还能咽下去饭
No one wants to eat with one of those staring at them.
我说  你真的觉得这样好吗
Come on, you can't seriously think that this is a good idea.
当然不好  但是我们答应过盖尔
Well, they're not for me, but we promised Gayle
画展期间可以在我们店展示她的作品
she could display her art for the art crawl.
说出去的话泼出去的水
We can't take it back now.
她很脆弱  我们得支持她
She's fragile. We have to support her.
能有多脆弱啊  琳
She's not that fragile, Lin.
怎么了  怎么了
What happened? What happened?
盖尔  盖尔  看  只是把叉子
Gayle, Gayle, honey, look, look, it's a fork.
-什么  -看  只是把叉子
- What? - Look, it's a fork.
是叉子啊
Oh, it's a fork. Ha.
你可吓死我了
Oh, you're killing me.
可吓死我了
She's killing me.
好吧  她确实很脆弱
Okay, so she's fragile.
为了她  我们就得满墙挂屁眼吗
And that means we have to be the anus restaurant?
没错  恐怕是
Yes, it means that.
我们可以做成T恤  在上面写
Oh, we can make T-shirts! It'll say:
牛奶牛奶柠檬汁
"Milk, milk, lemonade,
艺术就在街角制
around the corner art is made."
鲍勃  你是喜欢它们呢
Bob! Do you love 'em?
还是喜欢它们呢
Or do you just love 'em?
你怎么...
Um, how did you...?
你  为什么  要画  这个题材
Why... why would you paint... this?
我在山顶作画时得到的灵感
The inspiration came to me on a mountaintop.
画点什么好呢
What should I paint?
他很喜欢你的画
He loves 'em!
好了  听我说
All right, listen up.
画展上都是一些傻逼在转悠
All the suckers come out for art crawl.
他们还都想花钱买些垃圾货
And they all want to pay money for crap.
咱就画画这种货色  然后卖出去
So paint some crap, and we can sell it.
等等  你不动笔吗
Wait. You're not painting?
不  我是总经理
No, I'm management.
你俩负责画画  其余的我来处理
You two paint the stuff, I'll do the rest.
卖画
我去吆喝吆喝
I'll be wheeling and dealing.
赚的钱有我一份
I'll be getting my percent.
二十七分钟后
好了  让我看看你们都鼓捣出什么了
Okay, let's see what you got so far.
时间到  笔放下
Time's up. Paint brushes down.
这什么乱七八糟的
What the hell is this?
我不是说过要画些吸引游客的卖座垃圾吗
I told you to paint commercial touristy crap.
抱歉  我又不是畅销画家
I'm sorry I'm not a sellout.
我只画我感受得到的
I can only paint what I feel.
我也只画真相
And I can only paint the truth!
机器人要来了
The robots are coming!
快闪
Hide!
不错嘛
Ah, this is great.
你俩还真想当艺术家啊
You guys want to be real artists, huh?
好啊  不错的路线  可以以此为卖点
Okay, that's an angle. I can sell that.
要是你们真想成为艺术家
But if you're going artsy,
那就"艺术"到底
then you're going all the way.
必须有人奉献出一只耳朵
Someone's cutting off an ear.
我不能没有耳朵  因为我要戴眼镜
I need both of mine. I wear glasses.
你是什么借口
Welp, what's your excuse?
要割就都割了  画家要耳朵也没啥用
Don't got one. Have at it.
泰迪  你怎么了  怎么不吃呢
Teddy, what's wrong? You haven't touched your food.
我不知道  鲍勃  可能是因为...
I don't know, Bob. It's just the, uh...
那些屁眼吗
The anuses?
对  你懂的  没错  它们...
Yeah, you know. Yeah, they're, uh...
我懂的
I know.
它们就像蒙娜丽莎的双眼
Oh, they're like Mona Lisa's eyes.
你走到哪它们跟到哪
They follow you wherever you go.
你说的对
Ooh, you're right.
我喜欢它们
Well, I like them!
你居然喜欢
You like them?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah. What's the problem?
屁眼是臀部的窗户
The anus is the window of the butt.
说得好
It's true.
我想她只是把我们的心思画了出来
I guess she's just painting what we're all thinking.
好吧  但是  莫特
Well, okay, but, Mort,
你会把这些画挂在你的殡仪馆里吗
would you hang them up in your funeral home?
当然不会  那样会影响生意的
Of course not. That would be terrible for business.
我又不傻
I'm not an idiot.
数三下  但数到二就动手
Count to three, but do it on two.
我会把它冻起来的  直到画展结束
I'll keep it on ice until art crawl's over.
谢谢你  蒂娜
Thanks, T.
好了  听着  吉恩
Here goes. Now listen, Gene.
等下在割软骨的时候可能会有点费劲
I'm gonna have trouble cutting through the cartilage at first.
我割的时候  你就在心里想着你的艺术
While I'm doing it, just think about your art.
好
Okay!
很好  准备好了吗
All right. Ready?
忍者机器人  忍者机器人  忍者机器人
Ninja robot. Ninja robot. Ninja robot.
一  二
One... two...
-孩子们  -老爸
- Hey, kids. - Oh, hey, dad.
我要离开那些屁眼一会儿
I had to get away from those anuses for a while.
你是指莫特和泰迪吗
You mean Mort and Teddy?
不  不  是...  盖尔的那些画
No. No. Your... Gayle's paintings.
-你们几个小鬼在干嘛  -什么刀
- What are you kids doing? - What knife?!
什么什么刀  你干嘛拿把刀
What do you mean "What knife?" Why are you holding a knife?
我干嘛拿把刀
Why am I holding a knife?
她正要把我改造成一位真正的艺术家
She's turning me into a real artist.
她才不会  把刀放下
No, she's not. Put the knife down.
我想当艺术家
I want to be an artist!
像莱昂纳多・迪卡普里奥那样的艺术家
Like Leonardo DiCaprio.
美国演员
没错
That's right.
是达・芬奇才对吧  吉恩
That's Da Vinci, Gene.
不是
No!
把这些垃圾卖出的关键就在于
The only way I can sell this garbage
能否将它们合法化
is if I make them legit!
等一下  我有个好主意
Hey, wait a second. I have an idea.
你们知道谁喜欢你们画的画吗
You know who loves the stuff you kids draw?
是你吗
You?
不是  是你们老妈
No. Your mother.
这些垃圾对她来说就是猫薄荷
This crap is like catnip to her.
薄荷属植物  因其刺激性气味吸引猫而得名
她难以抗拒
She can't resist it.
把它们拿进去
Bring them inside.
好了  我们得在她们回来前把这些画挂好
All right, we need to get these up before they get back.
你们老妈看见这些画会很高兴的
Your mom will be so excited to see this stuff,
她甚至不会发现我把盖尔的画拿下来了
she won't even notice that I took Gayle's paintings down.
天衣无缝啊  老爸
Pretty manipulative, dad.
我终于明白我像谁了
I see where I get it.
谢谢  你应该知道我承担的压力
Thank you. You should see my taxes.
这是什么啊
Uh, what's this supposed to be?
史前巨石阵之
A ninja robot fighting
忍者机器人大战手动吸血录音机
a manipulative vampire tape recorder at stonehenge.
后面那个是谁啊
Who's that in the background?
-我朋友  肯  -为什么画成这样
- That's my friend Ken. - Why is he like that?
他有白化病
He's an albino.
是么
Oh.
是的
Yeah.
我没见过肯
I've never met Ken.
这人是真实的还是虚构的
Is he real or imaginary?
是真实的  他是玩即兴嘻哈的
He's real, and he does improvised hip-hop.
好吧  他多大了
Okay, how old is he?
二十八
He's 28.
你不可能有一个二十八岁的白化病朋友
You can't have a 28-year-old, albino friend.
就能就能
Yes, I can!
随便吧  我现在没心情管这个
All right, I can't deal with this right now.
蒂娜  你画的什么
Tina, what do you got?
我们的牙医
It's our dentist.
牙普医生吗  他怎么一丝不挂的
Dr. Yap? Why is he nude?
等一下蒂娜  他和你在一起时也这样吗
Wait, has he been nude with you, Tina?!
我加了些个人创意在里面
I exercised some artistic license.
咱还是换个题材吧
Uh, I... We're switching dentists.
不要
No!
我现在没心情管这个
I can't deal with that right now.
-可是...  -贴上来吧
- But... - Let's get them up.
琳达  盖尔  午餐怎么样
Linda, Gayle. How was lunch?
有趣极了
Very interesting.
那个服务员一直在跟我调情
I think the waiter might have been hitting on me?
是的  他非常殷勤
Yes. He was very attentive.
他还问了你许多关于食物的问题
And he asked you a lot of questions about food.
都问了些什么啊
What was that all about?
鲍勃 我的画呢
Uh, Bob? Where are my paintings?
什么  我得拿几幅下来
What? Wha-- Oh, I had to take a few down
给孩子们的画腾点地方
to make room for the kids' stuff.
鲍鲍  这是孩子们画的吗
Bobby! Aw, the kids' stuff!
咱这墙就好像一台大冰箱
Yeah. It's like our wall is a giant refrigerator.
我超爱
I love it.
天啊  鲍勃  如果我心眼小的话
Huh. Gee, Bob, if I didn't know any better,
我会觉得  是你不喜欢我的画
I'd think... you didn't like my paintings.
什么  不是的  我...
What, no? I...
不  不  不
No, no, no.
我知道你在骗我  鲍勃
I know when I'm being lied to, Bob.
这感觉就像我对镜中的自己说
It's like when I look at myself in the mirror and say,
一切都会好起来的
"It's going to be okay."
好吧  盖尔  那我就实话实说了
Fine, look, Gayle, I'm gonna level with you.
不不  鲍勃  不能说实话  不要
No, no, Bob. No, no leveling, no.
看好戏喽
Here we go.
-盖尔  关于你的画  -鲍鲍
- Gayle, the thing about your paintings... - Bobby! Ah...
你看  来了对老夫妻
Oh, look, senior visitors! Yay!
快看  是谁来了
Oh. Well, look who it is.
很好  是那家画店的
Great. The art store people.
是激情四射吗
Oh! Reflections.
我很喜欢你们店的
I love that store!
我也很喜欢你们的故事
I love your yarn.
请问您两位想来点什么
What can we get for you?
我不是给你送钱来的
I'm not here as a patron.
我是伊迪丝・格兰温可
I'm here as Edith Cranwinkle,
画展的主席
chairperson of the art crawl.
我急匆匆地赶来这里是因为听到些流言
I rushed right over here because there are murmurs.
街坊流言蜚语不断
Whispers and murmurs around town,
说你们...
that you're displaying...
在画展上陈列一些不雅之洞
certain offensive orifices during the art crawl.
不雅办公室
Offices?
不雅之洞
Orifices!
已经没有了
Not anymore.
我把那些画都拿下去了
I took them all down.
真叫人欣慰
Oh, what a relief.
我很高兴你能同意我这个决定
I'm glad you agree with my decision.
你的决定  什么决定
Your decision? What decision?
禁止在这里展示那种类型的画作
That you can't display that type of art here.
等等  禁止展示
Wait. I can't?
绝对禁止  多下流淫荡啊
Absolutely not! It's obscene.
下流淫荡
Obscene.
哎哟喂  你说什么
Oh, really?
你听到了  我说不行就不行
Yes. I won't allow it.
什么  你说不行就不行
Excuse me? You won't allow it?
没错  饭桶  你耳朵又不聋
That's right, tubsy. You heard her.
你们两个算老几
Who are you two to tell me
凭什么规定我家墙上能挂什么不能挂什么
what I can or can't hang on my wall?
我是画展的主席
I am chairperson of the art crawl.
那我还是这家餐馆的主席呢
Well, I'm the chairperson of this restaurant.
知道么  我要把那些画挂回去
And you know what? They're gonna go back up.
你敢
How dare you!
鲍鲍
Aw, Bobby!
吉恩  露易丝  去把画拿来
Gene, Louise, go get the paintings.
都在这里呢
Here they are!
欢迎进入屁眼壁橱
Step into the butt closet!
我才不要进去
I will not!
你应该试试
You should try it.
打死也不试
I will not!
怎么样你才能接受这只犀牛的屁眼呢
What's it going to take to get you into this rhino anus today?
你对我妻子出言不逊  鲍勃
You are in direct violation of my wife, Bob.
是么  有吗
Oh, I am, am I?
你看这招怎么样
Well, how about this?
马屁眼
Horse anus.
看着它
Look at it.
不
No!
鸡屁眼
Chicken anus.
不
No!
过来看
Take a closer look.
-狐狸屁眼  -哈罗德
- Fox anus. - Harold!
盖尔  我正式委托你创作新的屁眼画系列
Gayle, I'm commissioning a new series of anus paintings.
俩词儿  更大  更多
Two words... bigger and more.
滚
Out!
都给我滚
I cast you out.
我的老天
Oh, my gosh.
继续画  盖尔
Keep them coming, Gayle!
快好了
Almost done!
天啊  我觉得我都要和这幅画融为一体了
Oh, my, I feel like I could fall into this one!
鲍勃  我还以为
Bob, I thought
你不想把这里装扮成屁眼餐馆呢
you didn't want to become the anus restaurant.
我已经接受它了
Well, I've embraced it.
我们店就是屁眼餐馆  琳
We are the anus restaurant, Lin.
屁眼  屁眼  孩子们
A-nus! A-nus! Kids.
屁眼  屁眼  屁眼
A-nus! A-nus! A-nus!
这就对了  告诉你的朋友们吧
That's right! Go tell your friends!
不告诉也行  怎么做都行  都随你
Or don't. Either way. It's your choice.
你自找的  琳
Hey, you asked for this, Lin.
我只是照你的意思做的
I'm just doing what you wanted me to do,
支持你妹
support your sister.
说什么屁话
Oh, what a crock of crap!
你这么做
This is about you
不过是因为你自己的自尊还有那个伊迪丝
and your pride and that Edith.
你只是想激怒她
And you just want to provoke her.
真他妈对  我就这意思
Damn right, I do.
这幅画对你来说够大了吧  伊迪丝
This one big enough for you, Edith?!
开心汉堡店新鲜出炉的作品  闪亮登场
Fresh from their triumphant debut at Bob's burgers!
出售画作
没错  白粉级的画  白菜级的价
That's right, gallery-quality paintings at sidewalk prices.
艺术爱好者  来看看吧
Art lover, check this out!
那是牙普医生
Hey, that's Dr. Yap.
他是我的牙医  脸画得挺像  不过
He's my dentist. That's a good likeness in the face, but, uh...
身体比例不太协调
the proportions are off.
不  我觉得身体比例是正确的
No, I think the proportions are right.
我正在做成人牙套矫正术
Well, I'm getting adult braces.
-所以呢  -所以我应该知道
- So? - So I should know!
牙普医生身体矮小  双腿粗壮  他的躯干
Dr. Yap has short, strong legs, and his torso is...
我走了  滑冰去了
Well, I'm off to do some more roller-skating!
我已经为你们这俩杂牌画家尽力了
You know what? I've done all I can for you hacks.
你俩又不愿画畅销画
You refuse to paint touristy art,
老爸又不让我割掉吉恩的耳朵
dad won't let me cut off Gene's ear...
我们玩完了
We're through!
我们这下玩完了
We are through!
作为我的客户  我放弃你们
I'm dropping you as my clients,
作为我的哥姐  我要和你们断绝关系
and I'm dropping you as my siblings!
去上上艺术课吧  你们两个半吊子画家
Go take some art classes, you wannabes!
喂  安迪  奥利
Hey, Andy, Ollie.
还有你  红头发的
You, too, red.
给我过来
Come here.
你们玩没玩过这个游戏
You ever heard of the game,
名叫"你们画画我来卖"
"You guys paint whatever I say and then I sell it"?
赢的人会得到奥利的拥抱吗
Does the winner get a hug from Ollie?
安迪  你随时都能得到啊
Ah, Andy, you can have one of those any old time.
现在行吗
Now?
行了  别抱了  来画画吧
All right, stop hugging, let's paint!
我们来画贝壳  落日  和狗屎
Let's paint shells and sunsets and crap!
注意注意
Attention everyone!
画展协会不承认这家店的画作
This installation is not approved by the art crawl association.
太下流了  应该立即撤除
It's obscene, and should be taken down immediately!
我现在告诉你们
Well, I'll tell you this...
这幅画根本不需要什么画展协会的承认
It doesn't need to be approved by the art crawl association,
因为从现在开始这幅画将成为永久展示
because this is now a permanent installation.
永久展示
Permanent?
你会后悔的  鲍勃
You'll regret this, Bob!
你是在威胁我吗
Oh, is that a threat?
这才哪到哪  还没到威胁你的时候呢
Oh, when I threaten you, you'll know it!
Yeah, when she threatens you, you'll know it!
这算威胁么
Okay, was that a threat?
就是在威胁你
You bet it was!
你是想吓唬我么
Is that supposed to scare me?
当...
Defi...
...然是了
...Yes.
你要喝水吗
You want some water?
你家的水他死也不喝
He would never drink your water!
我真的需要
I really need s...
他没事
He's fine!
你没事
You're fine.
我得喝点水
I could use some water.
你没事
You're fine.
-鲍勃  给点水  -不行
- Bob, water. - No!
他就是死  也不会喝你们家的水
He'd rather die than drink your water!
-我不想死  -是的  他宁可死
- I wouldn't! - Yes, he would!
-我要喝水  -不能喝  哈罗德
- I'll drink it! - No water, Harold!
-求你了  -绝对不行
- Please! - Never!
伊迪丝
Edith!
难以置信  太疯狂了
Unbelievable. This is nuts.
真不敢相信伊迪丝会做出这种事
I can't believe Edith would do this.
我的艺术品
My artwork!
全毁了
It's ruined!
他们给这些动人的屁眼画上了内裤
They painted underpants on my beautiful anuses!
盖尔  盖尔  没必要大发脾气
Gayle, Gayle, no need to go off the deep end, okay?
你应该感到高兴才是
You should be flattered, right?
所有名家的作品都要经过审核的
All the great artists get censored.
-才不是呢  -是的是的  所有名家
- They do not. - Yes, yes! All of 'em do.
所有杰出画家都是这样的
Every... all the good ones.
天啊  真是让人措手不及
Oh, God, what a whirlwind we've been on.
把这页翻过去  我们向前看吧
I feel like let's just put this all behind us and move on.
-我要出去一趟  -什么  去哪
- I'm going down there. - What? Where?
去会会伊迪丝
To see Edith.
鲍鲍  别发疯
Bobby, don't do anything crazy.
我才没疯  是他们疯了
I'm not crazy, they're crazy!
不能就这么算了
And they're not gonna get away with it!
把那只贝壳粘在中间  安迪
Glue that shell in the middle, Andy!
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?!
我的手都抽筋了
My hand is cramping up!
我吃了太多的胶水
I ate too much glue!
安迪  奥利  过来
Andy, Ollie, come here.
我如此鞭策你们是因为你们有天赋  宝贝
Listen, I'm pushing you because you've got talent, babies.
我会关照你们的  相信我吧
And I'm gonna take care of you, oh, you better believe it.
但首先你们得为妈妈赚点钱
But first you've got to make some money for mommy.
好吗  我的宝贝
Okay, babies?
你也是  红头发  你叫什么  小甜心
You, too, red. What's your name, sweetheart?
-戴文・麦克吉姆  -闭嘴
- Devin McJim... - Shut up!
这不重要
It doesn't matter!
闭嘴  干活
Stop talking! Start working!
快干活  把贝壳粘在中间
Work! Shells go in the middle!
您来看
Here you go.
绝无仅有的原创作品
One-of-a-kind original.
帮帮这些可怜的残疾孤儿吧
Help support these poor, deformed orphans.
二十块
20 bucks.
老爸怒了
Dad's pissed.
休息五分钟
That's a take five.
说我自己呢  没说你们
For me! Not you!
快来看啊
Oh, look, everyone,
全市有名的色情画家
the town pornographer.
住口  伊迪丝  快跟我道歉
Can it, Edith. I'm here to get an apology.
我怎么了
For what,
就因为我支持艺术完整性和起码的礼貌吗
standing up for artistic integrity and common decency?
你做的事哪里礼貌了
There's nothing decent about what you did.
一开始  你就硬要规定我家墙上该挂什么
First you tried to tell me what to put on my walls,
后来你又任意破坏摧残
then you vandalized it.
难道你没有羞耻心吗
Have you no shame?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
-他也不知道  -什么
- And neither does he. - What?
揍她  老爸
Hit her, dad!
我不会揍她的  露易丝
I'm not gonna hit her, Louise.
揍她啊  老爸
Hit her, dad!
吉恩  蒂娜  你们俩在这儿干嘛
Gene? Tina? What are you two doing here?
学画画啊
Learning to paint.
我们在练手艺
We're honing our craft.
祝你化粪球为神器
Okay, well, good luck trying to polish a turd.
等等  我还以为你讨厌我的孩子呢
Wait, I thought you hated my kids.
我的店对所有尊重艺术的人开放
My artwork shop is open to all who respect art.
所以请你俩速速离开
So I'll have to ask you to leave.
-开口啊  -请离开
- Then ask me. - Please leave.
-不道歉我是不会走的  -你这辈子休想
- Not before I get an apology. - Not on your life!
随你便好了  艺术家
Have it your way, art lady!
用画笔戳她眼睛
Poke her in the eye with the brush.
我有个更好的主意  露易丝
Oh, I've got a better idea, Louise.
接招吧你
Ha-ha-ha! Take that!
老爸  那是啥啊
Dad, what is that?
屁眼啊
It's an anus.
还能是啥
What else would it be?
我们闹到现在不都因为它吗
What has this been all about?
你管那个叫屁眼
You call that an anus?
那就是个黑点啊
It looks just like a black dot!
这算哪门子屁眼
What kind of anus is that?
你这样说的话  哈罗德
Oh! Well, then, Harold,
看来我需要多加练习了
it looks like I'll need to practice a little more.
-我说...  -这里来一个如何
- I'll say. - How about one right here!
这里也来一个吧
And what about here!
这幅画也缺个屁眼
This one might need an anus!
这座灯塔也来一个
How about this lighthouse!
现在它有屁眼了
It has an anus now!
看起来不赖嘛  老爸
Looking good, dad.
谢了  蒂蒂
Thanks, Tine.
给那灯塔再来一个  老爸
Rip that lighthouse a new one, dad!
我充满了活力
I feel so alive!
上帝也有相同的感受吧
This is what God must feel like.
孩子们  告诉你们老妈别熬夜等我了
Kids, tell your mother not to wait up!
用棕色  用棕色
Use the brown! Use the brown!
你真应该看看当时的情况  妈妈
You should've seen it, mom.
老爸简直疯了
Dad went nuts!
鲍鲍  你做什么了
Aw, Bobby, what'd you do?
我主持了公道  琳
I got justice, Lin.
老爸给一座灯塔画了个屁眼
Dad painted an anus on a lighthouse.
对  还有一座山
Yeah. And on a Mountain
还有一副日落图  还有一支帆船
and on a sunset and on a sailboat...
-还有牙普医生  -还有肯
- And on Dr. Yap. - And Ken.
抱歉我也祸祸了你们的画  孩子们
Yeah, I'm sorry I painted on your paintings, kids.
它们只是被殃及的池鱼
They were in the line of fire.
你在那些画上画屁眼了
You painted anuses on paintings?
盖尔哪去了
Where's Gayle?
我要让她知道我有多么支持她
I got to tell her how I stood up for her.
她在地下室呢
She's in the basement
正努力把那些内裤从画上弄掉
trying to get the underwear off her paintings.
你不该去捣乱的  鲍勃
You shouldn't have done it, Bob.
开什么玩笑  琳
Are you kidding, Lin?
我这是我这辈子做过的最牛逼的事
It's the best thing I've ever done in my life.
看
Ow. See,
你就是这样戴上手铐的
that's how you put on handcuffs.
我看还不够紧呢
They don't look tight enough to me.
为什么铐我
Why are these on me?
因为你玷污了她的财产
Because you anally defaced her property.
但是是她先动手的  看看她的杰作
But she started it... look what she did.
这创意我喜欢
Oh. I like the new direction
我也想说是我做的
and wish I could take credit.
但我已经说过了  这不是我干的
But like I said, I had nothing to do with it.
好  咱走着瞧
Yeah, we'll see about that.
我要告你
I'm pressing charges.
我们法庭见吧
We're gonna take this to court!
等等  现在是你告她了吗
Wait, now you're charging her?
我搞不清了
This is confusing.
老爸会坐牢吗
Is dad going to jail?
-我会等你的  -给你点建议  老爸
- I'll wait for you. - Word of advice, dad:
千万别告诉狱友你是因为什么进去的
Don't tell your cell mate what you're in for.
我希望新爸爸是金发
I hope our new dad is a blond.
我受不了了
I can't take it anymore!
内裤不是伊迪丝画的  是我画的
Edith didn't paint the underwear! I did it!
什么  那些内裤都是你画的吗  琳达
What? You painted all those underpants, Linda?
我无法自已
Oh, I couldn't help it.
我一睡下那些屁眼就在我脑海里阴魂不散
Those anuses were haunting me in my sleep.
屁眼  屁眼  屁眼
Anus! Anus! Anus!
不
No...!
是你要我们支持你妹妹的
You were the one who said we had to support your sister.
我本来是支持她的  但后来我找到一种
I did support her, until I figured out a way
不伤害她感情又能毁掉那些画的方法
to destroy her art while preserving her feelings
还能把责任推到别人头上
and blaming someone else.
我觉得那些内裤看着特眼熟
I thought those looked familiar.
是啊
Oh, yeah!
老妈  你画的是你自己的内裤啊
Mom! You painted your own underwear!
什么  你怎么知道我的内裤什么样
What? How do you know what my underwear looks like?
我怎么会不知道
How don't I know?
她总是穿着内裤在房里走来走去
She wears it around the house,
得得瑟瑟  好像自己很完美似的
flaunting it, like she's all that.
我才没有
I do not!
好了  鲍鲍  我们去监狱吧
Okay, Bobby, let's go to jail.
等等  等等  等等  我能不能...
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Can't I...
伊迪丝  我赔你钱还不行吗
Edith, can't I just pay for the paintings?
你毁掉的东西的价值
Well, the retail value of what you destroyed
超过了一千美元
was over a thousand dollars!
那我们就给你二百块吧
We'll give you $200.
我们这周一个汉堡都没卖出去  琳
We haven't sold a burger all week, Lin.
我们没那么多钱
We don't have that kind of money.
交给我吧  老爸
I got this one, dad.
行了吗
Are we good here?
好吧  我收了
Fine! We'll take it.
这账我们稍后再算
Me and you can settle up later.
你从哪儿弄来那么多的钱
Where the hell'd you get all that money from?
嘘  别问  别问
Shh. Don't ask, don't ask.
-在画展上挣的  -可是...
- It's art crawl. - But...
露易丝
Louise.
-闭上嘴  -什么
- Shut your mouth. -What--
-画展上挣的  -可是我...
- It's art crawl. - But I...
-别说了  -但...
- Shh! Shut your mouth. - But the m...
-别说了  -我...
- Shut your mouth. - I...
我让你闭嘴  是画展上挣的
I said shut your mouth. It's art crawl.
走吧  哈罗德  别在这家破餐馆呆着了
Come on, Harold, let's get out of this ass parlor.
-熏死了  -好的
- It stinks! - Okay.
琳达  知道吗  如果你一开始
You know, Linda, none of this would have happened
就跟你妹妹坦白  这一切就不会发生了
if you'd just been honest with your sister.
没错  老妈  吉恩发胖那天起
It's true, mom. I've been honest
我就开始对这俩人坦诚以待了
with these two since the day Gene got fat.
我记得是冰淇淋三明治让我发胖的
I remember the ice cream sandwich that did it.
但我不后悔
I regret nothing!
蒂娜呢  每天口气都很重
And Tina... bad breath every day.
你喜欢鱼的话就不觉得重了
Not if you like fish.
看到没  他们多抗打击啊
See how tough they are?
我们已经没感觉了
We've been desensitized.
我已经麻木了
I'm so numb.
好吧  从现在开始
All right, from now on,
我要跟我妹妹说实话
I'm going to be honest with my sister.
她应该知道真相
She deserves to know the truth.
我做到了  我做到了
I did it! I did it!
我把画都改好了
I fixed all the paintings!
我给它们加了裤子和下垂的巨乳
I added pants and huge, pendulous breasts.
我好激动  我觉得这是我最棒的作品
Oh, I'm so excited! I think it's my best work ever.
你们觉得呢
What do you think?
给点反应啊
I'm not hearing anything.
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
盖尔  画很漂亮
Gayle, it's beautiful.
-棒极了  -棒极了  -很棒很棒
- They're great. - They look great. - Great. Great!
太好了
They're great!
-真梦幻  -没错  它们...
- Fantastic! - Yes, they are...
-看看哪  -非常  非常...
- Yeah, look at that! - Very, very...
我就知道  我就知道它们很出色
I knew it! I knew they were great!
拿着  你先把这些挂起来
Here, you hang these,
我现在下去把剩下的都画了
and I'm gonna go back down and finish the rest of 'em.
-我做不到  -换我我也说不出口
- Oh, I couldn't do it. - I wouldn't have done it.
实话实说也有例外的时候
There's exceptions to the honesty policy.
没错  没错  琳  你做的是对的
Yeah, yeah, I mean, Lin, you did the right thing.
谢谢你们支持我
Oh, thank you for supporting me.
我想抱抱大家伙
I want to hug each and every one of you!
-都过来  你们  到这来  -好吧
- Come here, all of you! Come on! - All right.
我爱我的家人
Oh, I love my family!
我爱你们
I love you!
爱够了没啊
Let me out of your love jail!
你觉得她还会回来吗
Do you think she's coming back?
我不知道  我要冻死了
I don't know. I'm so cold.
把我剖开  到我身体里取暖吧
Cut me open and crawl inside me.
-我们中总有人得活下来  -好吧
- One of us should live. - Okay.
老妈回来了
Mama's comin' back,
最好让我看到你们画的画
and mama better see some paintings!